{
    "id": "e72b3754cc274b75ac73d7300ebcdfc0",
    "title": "Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………………  the railway station is a very interesting place.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "think",
                "am thinking",
                "have thought"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6fdbe302ca0043a790758d90b1891971"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………..  there very often.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "am going"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fb564e6446474c14a44713812fc0cd98"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………….  to observe people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "am liking",
                "like",
                "have liked"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "222796e3b3df4522a34860f6c9877fac"
        },
        {
            "question": "A railway station ………………………….  the best place for this.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "has been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a33367e2bb3b4b70bd9533ca25b61468"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………. all kinds of people in a railway station.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "find",
                "will find",
                "have found"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "316f790b684f45c5b7c9184e935071d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "There ……………………… passengers, their friends, relatives, porters and even hawkers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "are",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8a9f6cfe1db14f3497849d8e0327d964"
        },
        {
            "question": "Babies and children who …………………….. with their parents are often the ones who enjoy the experience the most because they aren’t worried about the tickets, seats or luggage.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "travel",
                "traveling",
                "traveled"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9df2f67604ab430ab5ea6e14712d9718"
        },
        {
            "question": "Some travelers ………………………….. a lot of luggage.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "has",
                "are"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7f664832c67a4102a684c238c744d8ef"
        },
        {
            "question": "Others simply ……………………….. a backpack or a bag.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "carrying",
                "carry",
                "carries"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1679d79642e34756afbe877947484a72"
        },
        {
            "question": "The hawkers are a common sight in many of our railway stations. You can see them ……………………….. their handcarts all over the platform.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pushing",
                "to push",
                "pushed"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a2711411aae47c3b7b925ce8e1a8da6"
        }
    ]
}